ibuypower.com 2013-04-15

# iBUYPOWER Computer - Privacy Policy

Last updated: May 18, 2011

iBUYPOWER.com (“iBUYPOWER” or “We” or “Us”) respects your privacy. We know that you care how your information is used and distributed, and we appreciate your trust that we will do so carefully and sensibly. This notice describes our Privacy Policy. **By visiting iBUYPOWER.com and/or Dr. I Forum, you are accepting the privacy guidelines as described below.**

**What Personal Information Is Gathered?**  
The information gathered from customers is used to provide services to you, communicate with you about information you request, help us target specific offers to you, and/or help us personalize and continually improve your shopping experience at iBUYPOWER. The types of information we gather are:

  * **Information You Give Us** : We receive and store any information you enter on our website or give us in any other way (e.g. name, telephone numbers, shipping and billing addresses). The information you provide is mainly used for purposes such as responding to your requests, processing your order, customizing future shopping for you, and communicating with you. NOTE: We store credit card information in a separate, secure, and controlled accounting database to facilitate orders only. This database is NOT accessible through the Internet or from outside sources. However, upon request, we will gladly remove your credit card details from our database.
  * **Automatic Information (Cookies):** Like many websites, we use “cookies” to receive and store certain types of information whenever your Web browser accesses iBUYPOWER or advertisements and other content served by or on behalf of iBUYPOWER on other websites. Examples of what type of information are automatically collected include what pages you view, the links you click, the materials you access, and other actions taken within our website. ****
  * **Information from Other Sources:** We might receive information about you from other sources and add it to our account information (e.g. updated delivery and address information from our carriers or other third parties, credit history information from credit bureaus, etc). ****

**What About Cookies?**  
These cookies are alphanumeric identifiers that we transfer to your computer’s hard drive through your Web browser to enable our systems to recognize your browser. We use persistent, identifying cookies to remember your information and to link your activities to you. If you wish to disable the usage of cookies, you can easily do so by clicking the “help” button on the toolbar of your web browser and following the provided instructions. However, because these cookies enable you to successfully sign in, add items to your Shopping Cart, proceed to Checkout, and other essential website features, we recommend that you leave them turned on. If left disabled, iBUYPOWER will be unable to accept your online order.

**Do We Share the Information Collected?**  
Our customers’ information is an important part of our business, and we are not in the business of selling it to others. We only share customer information with: 

  * Third-Party Service Providers: We employ other companies and individuals to perform functions on our behalf (e.g. fulfilling orders, delivering packages, sending postal mail, providing marketing assistance, processing credit card payments, and providing customer service). They have access to personal information, but they may not use it for other purposes.
  * Business Transfers: As we continue to grow and develop our business, we might sell or buy business units, or engage in transfers, acquisitions, mergers, restructurings, changes of control or similar transactions. In such transactions, customer information is generally one of the transferred business assets but remains subject to the promises made in any pre-existing Privacy Notice.
  * Protection of iBUYPOWER & Others: We release account and other personal information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law; enforce or apply our Terms & Conditions and other agreements; or protect the rights, property, safety of our Site, our users, or others. This includes: exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection and credit risk reduction.
  * With Your Consent: You will receive notice when information about you might go to third parties, and you will have an opportunity to choose not to share the information.  

**How Secure Is Information About Me?**  
We take precaution to protect our customers’ information. When you submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and offline. We maintain physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards to secure your personal information. Secure Sockets Layer (SSL), 128-bit encryption, software is used to protect the security of your information during transmission by encrypting the information you input via the website. It is important for you to protect against unauthorized access to your password and to your computer. Be sure to sign off when finished using a shared computer. We recommend that you do not disclose your password to any other person. You are responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of your password and account, and are fully responsible for all activities that occur under your password and account. While we use reasonable efforts to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee absolute security. You should recognize, that no computer system is fully secure and that there are inherent risks associated with Internet transactions. Of course, any information you post in our Dr. I Forums or other public posting area on our website is available to anyone with Internet access. 

**What Information Can I Access?**   
Customers can view or change their own stored account information such as street address or e-mail address through our website under “My Account”. To make changes or access this information, you must have your e-mail address and password. 

**Can I Opt-Out?**  
It is your choice whether or not you want to receive e-mails or special offers from us. If you do not wish to receive e-mails from us, please contact our Customer Service Department or click the “Unsubscribe” link provided at the bottom of every newsletter sent via e-mail.

**Are Children Allowed to Use iBUYPOWER?**  
We do not sell products for purchase by children. If you are under 18, you may use our website only with the involvement of a parent or guardian.

**Privacy Policy Updates**   
We reserve the right to update our Privacy Policy from time to time. When we do, we will revise the “Last Modified” date at the top of this Privacy Policy. We encourage you to check this page periodically for any updates. Your continued use of this websites and Dr. I Forum following the posting of this Privacy Policy will mean you accept those updates.

**Contact Us**  
If you have any questions regarding our Privacy Policy, please contact our Customer Service Department.
